[SPEAKER_01]: Hello, Amy.
[SPEAKER_01]: I'm Dr. Jones.
[SPEAKER_01]: How are you doing today?
[SPEAKER_00]: I'm OK, but it hurts when I go to the bathroom when I pee.
[SPEAKER_01]: That's called dysuria, and it's pretty common.
[SPEAKER_01]: When did this start?
[SPEAKER_00]: Two days ago.
[SPEAKER_01]: Have you taken anything for it?
[SPEAKER_00]: I tried to Tylenol and drink cranberry juice and help.
[SPEAKER_01]: Have you had this before?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, I had this several years ago before you were my doctor.
[SPEAKER_01]: Do you remember about what year that was?
[SPEAKER_00]: Um, I think it was 2018.
[SPEAKER_00]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: How was it treated back then?
[SPEAKER_00]: The clinic gave me an antibiotic, um, bacterium, and that made it better.
[SPEAKER_01]: Great.
[SPEAKER_01]: Is there any chance that you're pregnant?
[SPEAKER_00]: I use protection, but there's always a chance, I guess.
[SPEAKER_01]: And so when was your last menstrual period?
[SPEAKER_00]: Uh, three weeks ago.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay.
[SPEAKER_01]: I think we should check a pregnancy test just to be sure.
[SPEAKER_01]: Have you had any vomiting, nausea, abdominal pain, back pain, shortness of breath, blood in your urine, constipation, diarrhea, or skin rashes?
[SPEAKER_00]: Yes, I've had abdominal pain down low.
[SPEAKER_01]: In any vaginal discharge or drainage or painful intercourse?
[SPEAKER_00]: No.
[SPEAKER_01]: Do you have any other problems that you'd like me to address?
[SPEAKER_01]: No.
[SPEAKER_01]: Okay, I would like to do a simple physical exam and have you give us a urine sample.
[SPEAKER_01]: I will order both pregnancy tests and urine tests and that we will do now and determine treatment when we have the results.
[SPEAKER_01]: Does that sound okay to you?